<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF8" ?>
<texts>
<text id="0">Here's your book.</text>
<text id="1">Good day</text>
<text id="2"></text>
<text id="3">Good day, all this talk about the Legend is strange, don't you think?</text>
<text id="4">Very strange indeed. I'm just an old fool who would like to grow flowers in the desert, but... I know about this Legend that Dr. FunFrock forbade. I'll tell you what I know if you bring me a sacred book. It is in the Temple of Bù which was buried by a violent sand storm. You can still get in, however, through one of the ventilation shafts still visible just behind me. But be careful: there is danger everywhere!</text>
<text id="5">This book is a keeper of knowledge. It allows you to read the rocks and to talk to the animals. </text>
<text id="6">To Principal Island.</text>
<text id="7">I'll leave later on.</text>
<text id="8">I can get you to where you want to go for only 10 Kashes! Where do you want to go?</text>
<text id="9">Sorry, Twinsen, you don't have enough Kashes.</text>
<text id="10">To Citadel Island.</text>
<text id="11">Thanks for opening the grotto. My name is Joe the Elf. I was locked up here because I wasn't meant to be in the story, there might have been some bugs in the game!</text>
<text id="12">See you later, and thanks again.</text>
<text id="13">You're too aggressive! Come back later when you've calmed down.</text>
<text id="14">Ow, you crazy or what? You don't deserve to be an elf, give me your membership card!</text>
<text id="15">Where do you want to go?</text>
<text id="16">Home.</text>
<text id="17">Proxima island.</text>
<text id="18">Rebellion island.</text>
<text id="19"></text>
<text id="20"></text>
<text id="21"></text>
<text id="22"></text>
<text id="23"></text>
<text id="24"></text>
<text id="25"></text>
<text id="26"></text>
<text id="27"></text>
<text id="28"></text>
<text id="29"></text>
<text id="30"></text>
<text id="31"></text>
<text id="32"></text>
<text id="33"></text>
<text id="34"></text>
<text id="35"></text>
<text id="36"></text>
<text id="37"></text>
<text id="38"></text>
<text id="39"></text>
<text id="40"></text>
<text id="41"></text>
<text id="42"></text>
<text id="43"></text>
</texts>
