<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF8" ?>
<texts>
<text id="0">I have you at last! I see that you appreciated the clone that I made of your friend, the original is safe. @ I suppose that you have come here to find the 3rd Runic Stone. I already found it a long time ago, but it took some time to decipher it. And as soon as I knew the location of the Well of Sendell, I began the foraging work. @</text>
<text id="1">Not being able to destroy the stone, I built my fortress around it to dissimulate it. That reminds me, you supposedly destroyed two of my factories, but that is of little importance! I will soon possess such fantastic powers, that I will need but an instant to clone or teleport the totality of the inhabitants of the planet. I also can make you relive the worst moments of your existence indefinitely... @ Good bye, you will never realize the prophecy because I will be the one who encounters Sendell and I will inherit her powers.</text>
<text id="2">I am the stone of the Septentrion. The Well of Sendell is located at the summit of the rocky peak that is at the center of Polar island. Only the Heir can break the seal that bars the entrance. </text>
<text id="3">Help Twinsen ! They found the Runic Stone and I ...</text>
<text id="4">Ah, there you are at last my love!</text>
<text id="5">I don't know where they are, but hurry up because FunFrock is going...</text>
<text id="6">Don't know who rigged the telepods, I just succeeded in picking the lock of my cell, and I ended up here!</text>
<text id="7">Their teleportation thingamajig is all smashed up. I was walking, minding my own business, in the Hamalayi mountains, and suddenly I end up here!</text>
<text id="8">Hi</text>
<text id="9">Stop fidgeting prisoner Twinsen!</text>
<text id="10">A prisoner is escaping! @ Sound the alarm!</text>
<text id="11">You've just rediscovered all the objects in your inventory!</text>
<text id="12">Good day.</text>
<text id="13">Dr FunFrock's secret Fortress. You shouldn't even be reading that! </text>
<text id="14">Hmmm, what if I tried to attract a guard's attention?</text>
<text id="15">You are being held here because you are a troublemaker. We know from an informant that you claim to have prophetic dreams. @ Calm down, we're going to dissect... uh, I mean take care of you!</text>
<text id="16">Uh ... Hi!</text>
<text id="17">Training pool. Do not throw anything to the shark! </text>
<text id="18">Draining valve. DO NOT TOUCH! </text>
<text id="19"></text>
<text id="20"></text>
<text id="21">To Tippett island.</text>
<text id="22">To Brundle island.</text>
<text id="23">To the Hamalayi mountains.</text>
<text id="24">I'm staying here.</text>
<text id="25">Where do you want to go Twinsen ? </text>
<text id="26">I know that symbol on your medallion. Virgul, our sorcerer, told us about your coming, and we have often prayed in front of the Runic Stone, which carries the same symbol. Unfortunately, Dr. FunFrock found it and built his fortress right over it, although the Rock was supposed to be indestructible! I would dig a tunnel for you so that you could enter the building, but you must first sabotage the Teleportation Center. Go find the plans of this center, I can dig only after all the telepods have been neutralized!</text>
<text id="27">I don't know where they are, but with these plans you must enter the Center on Brundle island and then sabotage it. Then I can dig under the Fortress!</text>
<text id="28">Go to Brundle island, get in the Center and neutralize the telepods control system.</text>
<text id="29">Good going, the telepods are no longer working, follow me!</text>
<text id="30">You're the one that's making life difficult for FunFrock? He recently threw a tantrum that could be heard from here. Since then, he brought in several telepods, he's worried about his fortress.</text>
<text id="31">You have once again angered FunFrock, he screamed a little while ago! What did you break this time, you know that he hates you?</text>
<text id="32">I don't know where they are, ask your flying animal over there. In fact, can you eat that animal?</text>
<text id="33">We no longer fear the threat of the teleportations, but you must get rid of the guards and the assault tank for us. I will then be able to dig.</text>
<text id="34">Good luck!</text>
<text id="35">Get out!</text>
</texts>
