<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF8" ?>
<texts>
<text id="0">Twinsen help! I'm not a clone, it's me, the real Zoé.</text>
<text id="1">You must break the seal so that I can enter the Well of Sendell. None of my machines could drill through this rock, it resists me, just like the Runic Stone. I began digging around the rocky peak, but it will take months for me to reach the center of the planet! You'll see, I will realize the prophecy myself, and I'll take good care of this planet. Break the seal and I'll spare you Twinsen, you and your friend.</text>
<text id="2">I will at last see Sendell's face. If everything goes as planned, I'll make you my jester when I come back. Ha, ha, ha!</text>
<text id="3">Before you destroy the cloning factory, I prepared THIS for you!</text>
<text id="4">At last, you took your time, my love. I'm not escorted by two groboclones, but I promise that it's really me. Go find Sendell and then we'll go home.</text>
<text id="5">Good day. </text>
<text id="6">I am Sendell, like all of those you see here, we are all Sendells. We are here to watch over a stellar entity that is in gestation, it will come into existence in a few centuries. As we can only act from the heart of the planet, we implanted a lineage of elected creatures among the species living on the surface. You are the current descendant of this family, and when FunFrock's threat had become too great, it was me that called to you in your dreams. The entity can now finish its gestation because you rid us of FunFrock. It would have died if he had gotten to it, and this world would have imploded, thanks to you it will continue to flourish. Return now to the surface, you can now erase the final traces that he left there.</text>
<text id="7">Twinsen, NO! We are finished, don't let him reach us!</text>
<text id="8">Uh ... you might be surprised when you discover the house.</text>
<text id="9">What are you doing there? The route that connects the 2 islands is classified top secret.</text>
<text id="10">Can't start this machine without an ignition key!</text>
<text id="11">Here, little guy, take the ignition key and bring the bulldozer back for me - I'll appreciate it. I don't have time to do it myself.</text>
<text id="12">This work is not moving along fast!</text>
<text id="13">You have to try out this Champagne. Cuvee speciale. Thats some strong stuff we got here.</text>
<text id="14">Its time for celebration! Come over here I might have something for you.</text>
<text id="15">Merry Christmas!</text>
<text id="16">Happy new year!!</text>
<text id="17">Don't mind me I am just an extra. They only put me there because I have a nice looking suit.</text>
<text id="18">They are throwing a pretty big party over there. You might want to have a look at it!</text>
<text id="19">I am stuck inside the ground ever since I uncovered this statue. Everybody is gone to the party without even noticing me! Could you please give me a hand?</text>
<text id="20">Santa doesn't want to give me any gift... I am sure he is keeping all of them for himself!</text>
<text id="21">Ho Ho Ho! Meeeery christmas kid! Have you been nice this year? Oh whatever, just choose a present and get yourself moving. The next pleeeaaase? Oh man I sooo start to hate this job...</text>
<text id="22">Never seen a talking snowman?? Anyway you might want to talk to santa over there.</text>
<text id="23">Bye</text>
<text id="24">Lets talk about something else...</text>
<text id="25">OK show me what you have...</text>
<text id="26">Please please pleeeeaaaassse!! I was very nice this year...</text>
<text id="27">We are going to play all night! Could you go fetch me some more coffee please.</text>
<text id="28">This guitar is fabulous! It was totally worth the price I got it from this weird ponytail guy.</text>
<text id="29">Don't you see you are interrupting something... Go away!</text>
<text id="30">Man. This is so good. I can't get enough of it!</text>
<text id="31">Hey sweetie! What are you waiting for? Come to dance with us!</text>
<text id="32">Why are you staring at me like that! Everybody needs to have a litle break from time to time. Anyway, tonight is party night. Let's dance baby!</text>
<text id="33">We whish you a merry christmas...</text>
<text id="34">Man... I have no idea what I am doing here. And this music is so loud... Anyway, want to have a drink?</text>
<text id="35">And an happy new year!</text>
<text id="36">Sorry - hips -  I don't talk to funny looking strangers. buurps! You and your twin - hips - can leave me alone!</text>
<text id="37">Yeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeehaaaaaah!!!!!!!</text>
<text id="38">I just teleported back to the reality. The Lbanet team is giving you their best wishes for the new year! Cheers!</text>
<text id="39">We whish you a merry christmas...</text>
</texts>
